让我们来谈谈有关权限的问题  当每个应用程序的APK被安装的时候
Let's talk about permissions, when each app APK is installed,
它被给予了它自己的特有的Linux用户ID
it's given it's own unique Linux user ID. And each
并且每个应用都运行在自己的Androi虚拟机实例中
app runs within its instance in the Android Virtual machine.
因此每个应用程序是完全被沙箱隔离的
[SOUND] As a result each app is completely sand boxed.
它的文件处理和其他的资源是其他应用程序不能访问的
Its files processes and other resources are inaccessible
这个沙箱的运作方法确保了在默认情况下
to other apps. This sandboxing approach is used to
没有任何应用程序可以访问到敏感的数据
ensure that by default no app can access sensitive
或执行可能对其他的应用程序  系统  或用户产生
data or perform actions that could adversely impact other
不利影响的操作  比如说像访问互联网
apps, the OS, or users. Things like accessing the
获取用户的地点  读取或修改联系人的数据库
internet, getting the user's location, or reading or modifying
这些操作  比起应用每次访问敏感数据
the contacts database. Rather than asking the user each
的时候都询问一下用户
time an app tries to access something sensitive you
你应该在manifest配置文件中声明你的应用需要的权限
declared permissions that your app requires in it's manifest.
你可以从Android开发者网站上
You can get a list of all of the permission
获取你的应用可能需要的所有权限的列表
your app may require here at the Android developer site.
所以  为什么不请求所有的权限
So, why not just ask for all the permissions and
而再也不用担心权限问题呢  是的  当用户安装
never worry about it again? Well, when users install
你的应用程序的时候  他们会看到这个列出了你申请
your app they greeted with this dialogue which lists all
的所有权限的对话框  这些权限使了用户
of the permissions that you've requested along with the more
更易理解的描述  没有应用程序会在这里说它是黑客专门
user-friendly descriptions. Nothing says this app was built by hackers
用来窃取我数据  抢劫我房子  清空我账户
who want to steal my data, rob my house, clear out my
并且拍摄和分享我的裸露的照片的
bank account, and take and share nude pictures of me like
就比如一个想获取设备上所有权限的天气应用
a weather app that wants access to every permission on the
最好的做法是只请求需要的权限
device. Best practice is to request the absolute minimum of permissions.
每次你需要请求一个新的权限
Every time you need to request a new permission, take it
停下来思考一下  是否有其他的
as a flag to stop and consider if there are other
替代方案可以达到同样的目的  例如
alternatives that might achieve the same goal. For example, using an
使用Intent来启动照相机  而不是直接访问照相机
intent to launch the camera app, rather than accessing the camera, directly.
之后我们会看一些与其他应用程序共享数据的方法
Later, we'll look at ways to share your data with
使用Intent和ContentProvider架设起应用程序沙盒
other apps, using intents and content providers to create bridges
之间的桥梁  你同样可以在这些实例上
between these apps sandboxs. You can declare and use those
声明和使用这些权限
permissions in these instances to
去限制访问用户的敏感信息
similarly restrict access to sensitive information.